(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Raj:)Me, too.
(Raj:)Good times.
(Penny:)16 wants to order appetizers.
(Bernadette:)Oh, thanks.
This was nice.
(Penny:)What the hell are you doing?
(Penny:)Howard is your best friend,
and that is his girlfriend.
(Penny:)You should be
ashamed of yourself.
(Raj:)I was when I came in,
(Raj:)but it's amazing what
liquor does to guilt.
(Raj:)Besides what you
might not know
(Raj:)is Bernadette is planning on
breaking up with Howard.
(Penny:)Well, I know that. How do you know that?
My sister told me.
(Penny:)Oh, that gossipy bitch.
(Penny:)No offense.
(Raj:)None taken.
(Raj:)You should hear how
she talks about you.
(Penny:)Okay, listen, just because Howard
and Bernadette are having problems,
(Penny:)does not mean you should
be here sniffing around.
(Raj:)What can I do?
(Raj:)I can't stop
thinking about her.
(Penny:)All right, try
thinking about this--
(Penny:)Sheldon and Amy had sex.
(Raj:)Shut your ass!